(Title: Saebit Day Plans,
Bazaar, New Light Prince)
Okay, guys. At the count of three,
you're going to choose someone, okay?
One, two,
three.
What are you doing, Shin-Woo?
Do you want to be the prince?
Yes!
Then, with a unanimous vote,
the participant for the New Light
Prince Contest this year will be...
Woo Tae-Gyeong!
Give him a round of applause.
Congratulations, Tae-Gyeong.
No way.
(Saebit Boy High School Meeting)
You guys planned it...
while I was in the bathroom, right?
You agreed to choose me, right?
What are you talking about?
What do you take us for?
When you were in the bathroom,
we didn't do anything.
We just sat here.
Right, Shin-Woo?
I'm sorry.
I knew it.
We need good teamwork to pull off a con.
Why are your ears so red?
They're like a lie detector test.
That's why I told you
we shouldn't do it.
I'm sorry, Tae-Gyeong.
But it's because you're the only person
that can do it.
But what's the New Light Prince?
Well...
Saebit Day is the charity event
hosted by Saebit Foundation.
During that event, the part
that raises the most donations is...
the New Light Prince Contest.
That's what they say.
If I were to give you more details,
it's exactly what it sounds like.
They choose the most handsome
and popular person for it.
It's tradition for someone
in the student council to do it.
Da-On, who couldn't make it
because of his exams,
won last year.
It was incredible back then.
In any case,
the New Light Prince this year...
will be Tae-Gyeong.
He's very handsome, just like me.
What are you talking about?
Why are you worried, Tae-Gyeong?
I'm sure you will win.
The best stylist ever, me, Namkung,
will help you,
so don't worry.
You don't have to wear your uniform.
I have to prepare an outfit
and go on stage all by myself?
I'm really bad at that.
Don't worry about that.
You will have a manager
to help you with everything.
Who is it?
It's Noh Shin-Woo.
What?
Shin-Woo will be Prince Tae-Gyeong's...
manager.
Give him a round of applause.
That's a great idea.
This is great, Tae-Gyeong.
Right.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Yes, of course.
Then do you want to meet at
K Shopping Mall at 12 tomorrow?
Sure.
What about lunch?
Are you going to eat first?
No. Let's eat together.
Okay.
- Also...
- What?
What are you going to wear tomorrow?
Why are you asking me about that?
I'm going to be dressed
in an effortlessly chic look.
What does it mean
to be effortlessly chic?
I'm just going to wear whatever I see.
How have you never heard of
the effortlessly chic look?
Is that so wrong?
Everyone these days knows what that is.
- Do you know everything?
- Of course I do.
Plus, I'm not a picky eater.
Da-On. What are you doing?
Is that for me?
- What?
- Nothing. I'm just kidding.
Let's go eat
in the student council room.
(Chats, Noh Shin-Woo)
(Tae-Gyeong leave the chatroom.
Leave. Did you do it?)
(I'm not going to do it.)
Is he ignoring me?
(Enter search words.)
(The meaning of effortlessly chic)
(It means you're dressed up
but not too dressed up.)
(Dressed up but not too dressed up)
"Dressed up but not too dressed up"?
(The meaning of effortlessly chic)
What does that mean?
(Tae-Gyeong: Don't be late tomorrow.)
(Tae-Gyeong)
(Don't be late tomorrow.)
He's ignoring me again?
(Go to bed.)
Wait.
Darn it.
I read it right away.
What if he thinks I was waiting
for his text?
"How to go on a nice date".
(The first tip
on having a successful date.)
(Look at them in the eyes while having
a conversation.)
(Be sure to nod and show that
you can relate to them.)
(Cupid of Love's answer)
Tae-Gyeong.
I'm sorry.
Did you wait long?
Yes. Why were you so late?
I overslept.
You never oversleep.
I went to bed late last night.
I'm sorry.
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
I'm wondering if this is
your effortlessly chic look.
You got pretty dressed up today.
Were you late because
you were choosing this outfit?
I picked it out last night.
You picked it out last night?
So you overslept because
you were picking this out?
Be quiet. Let's go.
Teasing him is pretty fun.
What do you think about this?
(Look at them in the eyes while having
a conversation.)
(Be sure to nod and show that
you can relate to them.)
Is it okay?
What about this one?
What about this?
How about this?
Are you broken?
You don't want to be my manager, do you?
I mean, no. It's not that.
Fine. I'm glad you're being honest.
Let's just look around here and go.
No. Let's look at everything.
I didn't even eat.
We agreed to eat together.
I wanted these.
Does it clash with our concept?
Why do you keep doing that?
What?
You keep glaring at me.
And when I ask you something,
you just nod insincerely.
If you're going to do that,
just go home.
Are you mad?
Yes.
You came here to help me,
but you weren't helpful.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
You must be tired
because you didn't get a lot of sleep.
You can go home after we drink this.
I'll just look around
some more by myself...
No!
I want to stay here...
with you.
I want to be here with you.
Oh, well...
After seeing the clothes you chose,
I thought youⒹ need some help.
Oh, right. Fine.
Here.
Are these for me?
Yes.
I just wanted to get you a present.
Wear these
and don't be nervous on stage.
As for the clothes...
You looked good in everything.
You have a small face,
you're pale,
and you're handsome.
Oh, right. Well...
I need to buy a hat.
Can you help me choose one out?
Oh, my. It's cute.
It looks really cute.
I'll take a photo for you.
Hey.
Do you...
want to take one with me?
Sure.
(Slightly less handsome Tae-Gyeong)
(What do you think of this hat?
Noh Shin-Woo picked it out.)
I chose a great manager for him.
- What?
Oh, well...
Tae-Gyeong...
is going to participate
in the New Light Prince Contest.
I thought heⒹ struggle on his own,
so I had Shin-Woo
help him has his manager.
I see. Good job.
How are things between
you and Tae-Gyeong? Did you guys talk?
- Not yet.
- Da-On!
- What?
- Don't look at me like that.
You look really sad,
so it makes you look handsomer.
You make me laugh.
Right. You should smile like that.
You're almost as handsome as me,
so when you smile, you look quite nice.
So?
When are you going to talk to him?
I want to talk to him in person,
but we never bump into each other.
That makes sense.
You can't come to the student council
room because of your exams,
and you're in a different grade.
Shin-Woo and Tae-Gyeong
are always together,
so they fight
and make up really quickly.
Are you going to contact him?
No. There's another way.
Right. You always know what to do.
I'll see you later, Namkung.
Where are you going all of a sudden?
Something suddenly came up.
I'm really sorry.
Gosh, we did a great job shopping today.
I'm going to win no matter what.
I'm sorry.
I sincerely want to apologize...
for what I did to you.
I was envious of you.
I liked Da-On before you,
but it seemed like Da-On...
liked you more than me.
I thought that you were stealing
Da-On from me.
Da-On doesn't even belong to me.
I...
can't say that it's okay right now.
But it will become okay.
We have something in common.
We both really like Da-On.
I don't.
Who does something like that
to someone they like?
I have no right to like him.
Do you remember what you said to me?
Hi. It's been three years
since I liked Sin Da-On.
My name is Lee So-Hee.
When I met you, this is what I thought.
"Gosh, she's so honest and cool."
That's when...
I wanted to become friends with you.
Out of all the people that I know,
you're the most courageous...
and coolest person.
So let's become friends one day, okay?
We could become friends from now on.
To celebrate becoming friends...
Here.
What is this?
I heard you were participating
in the New Light Prince Contest.
Namkung told me.
Right.
I got it because I thought
it would look good on you.
Thank you, So-Hee.
Don't be.
I'm more grateful, Tae-Gyeong.
I'll get going.
Okay. Goodbye.
Okay. I'll see you around.
What are you thinking about?
Just...
I wonder what Da-On is doing right now.
So-Hee said it's been a while
since she saw Da-On too.
He doesn't answer her calls either.
Is he okay?
Do you miss him?
I just...
want to know if he's doing okay.
I'm worried.
I know you don't want to see me.
But can you just give me
a moment of your time?
After what happened between us,
I couldn't sleep,
and I couldn't eat.
I thought IⒹ be more tormented
if I didn't say anything.
I'm sorry for putting you through
all that pain...
just because I liked you.
I'm sorry for hurting
the person you like.
You can stay mad at me if you want,
and it's okay if you hate me.
But...
I'm not okay with you saying
you never want to see me again.
So-Hee.
I understand, so stop crying.
Your eyes are going to get swollen.
I don't hate you.
I'll take back what I said about
never seeing you again.
But...
I don't think we can
be good friends right now.
Right.
I can wait.
Were you going somewhere?
To meet someone.
Is it Woo Tae-Gyeong?
Tae-Gyeong is a good guy.
I can see why you like him now.
Right.
I know that Tae-Gyeong is a good guy.
That's why...
I'm going to start all over again.
You went through so much trouble
being my manager...
and shopping with me.
Thank you.
Thanks for the shoes too.
Hey, Tae-Gyeong.
Yes?
I'm sure you know this,
but I'm bad...
at expressing myself.
That's why when I met someone
as honest as you,
I thought it was interesting at first,
and I got curious,
and...
I wanted to spend more time with you.
So?
Right, so...
What I want to say is...
I...
am not disqualified as your manager,
right?
Right. You'll continue to be my manager.
You have to stay by my side every day
and answer all of my questions...
and do everything I tell you to do.
Hey, that's...
So...
don't worry and go home and sleep.
You didn't lose your job.
I had a lot of fun today.
I'll see you at school.
"Stay..."
"by my side."
He knows
how to make a person's heart flutter.
Hi,
Tae-Gyeong.
=Light on Me=
(How are things between you and Da-On?)
What do you think? Do we seem awkward?
It's an hour before the contest.
Where did it go? Where is it?
- Are you looking for something?
(- Did something happen?)
(Tae-Gyeong.)
Shin-Woo...
=Light on Me=